# **Jordan Chan**

# Web Developer

jordancmchan@hotmail.com • 647-393-8506 • LinkedIn • GitHub • codenamej.com

### **SUMMARY**

Hi, I'm Jordan and I am a developer based in Toronto. Coming from a background in retail management, I understand the dynamics of a team based workplace where we work to achieve a common overall goal. I am a team oriented, self-driven manager with over 5 years of experience. I believe my solid foundation in multitasking, time management, and communication skills can be transferred into any industry.

## **EDUCATION**

Juno College, Toronto, ON, Canada

2020 - 2021

Web Developer Full Time Immersive Boot Camp

Javascript Course - Accelerated

Intro to Web Dev

George Brown College, Toronto, ON, Canada

2012 - 2013

Culinary Skills Chef Training

# **SKILLS**

Javascript

• HTML

- React
- Firebase
- Rest APITerminal
- Problem Solver

• CSS

• SASS

- TerminalTeam Management
- AdaptableCooking

PROJECTS

## **Random Plants with Big Names**

HTML, CSS, Javascript, SASS

A project that was used to understand useState and useEffect alongside fetching the API to choose and display certain and random characters. Functionally working, design is a work in progress

• Live Link

Github Link

#### Sun Run

React, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Moments Node, SASS, Terminal, Rest API

The Sun Run app will enable users to check the time of sunrise and sunset depending on which timezone and date they select. User will be also be shown what time to leave for a run before to catch the sunrise or sunset

• Live Link

• GitHub link

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Club Monaco, The Eaton Centre

2019 - 2020

Stock Manager

- Created and established day to day opening and closing procedures to ensure tasks, organization and cleanliness were kept up to store standards
- Managed a team of 13 individuals to ensure various tasks deployed from head office and management team such as transfers, markdowns and replenishments were completed within the allotted timeframe

#### MUJI Canada, The Atrium & Markville Mall

2015 - 2019

Assistant Store Manager, Department Manager, Sales Associate

- Worked collaboratively with store manager and head office on all store aspects including operational and administrative tasks, sales, visuals, inventory, training and customer service
- Coached and strategized with department leads to develop a deeper understanding of store performance using analytics and data
- Chosen by MUJI's global office to support the expansion of the MUJI brand in Canada, collaborating with different functions worldwide successfully open multiple retail stores within the GTA and BC area